fresheropenings.com 2019-12-21

# Privacy Policy

**Social Networking Integration**

The Services contain joining with interpersonal organizations and different stages in which data is shared among us and such stages. For instance, on the off chance that you make or sign into your record through an outsider online life website, we will approach certain data from that webpage, for example, your name, email address, account data, photograph and companions records, and other data as per the approval strategies dictated by such web based life website. On the off chance that you visit our Services on a gadget through which you likewise collaborate with interpersonal organizations or on the off chance that you associate with us through an internet based life capacity, for example, a module (for instance, a Facebook “like” catch) at that point you allow us to have on-going access to, to utilize and to store data from your informal organization profile, (for example, your name, email address, and the general population/destinations you pursue) as per this Privacy Policy. On the off chance that you don’t need an interpersonal organization to gather the data about you as portrayed above, or you don’t need an informal organization to impart it to us, it would be ideal if you survey the protection strategy, security settings and directions of the relevant informal organization before you visit and utilize our Services.

**Cookies**

A ‘Cookie’ is a ‘Non-Personal Information’ that is not personally identifiable to you and that we automatically collect when you access our website with a web browser. It is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows Fresheropenings.com to recognize you each time you visit or login to this site.We use Google Analytics for this purpose. Google Analytics uses its own cookies. It is only used to improve how our Services works. Fresheropenings.com does not use cookies to store visitor’s information. Third party services such as Google Adsense and Google Analytics store cookies to track visitors and for better ad management. For any concern with a third party, please contact them directly.

**External Links:**

Fresheropenings.com does provide links to other websites that are not under our direct control. Once you have left Fresheropenings.com and landed on another site, then it’s their privacy policy that comes into action. We won’t be able to control a user’s privacy on another site. The Services contain links to other websites that we do not control, and the Services contain videos, advertising and other content hosted and served by third parties. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of any third-party. We cannot also be held liable/accountable for any loss/damage occurring as a result of activity on another website.

**Protection Policy Updates:**

We maintain whatever authority is needed to change this protection arrangement whenever. You should survey this Privacy Policy as often as possible. On the off chance that we roll out material improvements to this arrangement, we may tell you on our Website, by a blog entry, by email, or by any technique we decide. The strategy we picked is at our sole prudence. We will likewise change the “Last Updated” date toward the start of this Privacy Policy. Any progressions we make to our security approach are powerful as of this Last Updated date and supplant any earlier Privacy Policies.

**Inquiries related to Privacy Policy:**

In the event that you have any inquiries regarding our security practices or this strategy, if you don’t mind write us at Fresheropenings.com@gmail.com
